Roshani Kumari

Graphic & UI/UX Designer



CONTACT



roshanikumari068@gmail.com



+917273880372

SKILLS

- Graphic Design
- UI/UX Design
- Web Design
- Stop Motion
- Doodling

TECHINICAL SKILLS

- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe After effects
- Adobe Indesign
- Figma
- Adobe Dimension

LENGUAGE

- Hindi
- English

ABOUT ME

As a skilled graphic designer with six months of industry experience, I have a proven ability to create engaging and visually stunning designs using Adobe Creative Suite. In addition to my graphic design skills, I also have a working knowledge of UI/UX design. My ability to combine both design disciplines allows me to create designs that are not only visually appealing but also intuitive and user-friendly.



EDUCATION

2019 - 2023 Chitkara University, Punjab

Bechelor of Design (B.des), Visual Communication Design



EXPERIENCE

2022- 2023 Bajaj Finserv Health Limited

(6 Months) Jr. Graphic Designer

2021 - 2021 Shining Tomorrow Foundation

(3 Months) Graphic Designer



PORTFOLIO

Be https://www.behance.net/Roshanikumarii



INTEREST







TRAVEL

MUSIC

Drawing & Painting